Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music collection
  - 12 inch vinyl
    - Numbered by Bambaataa
      Series contains vinyl discs and jackets that were annotated with a number assigned by Bambaataa. The items are arranged according to the number Bambaataa assigned them. Some jackets have more than one vinyl record and both vinyl discs aren’t always numbered. Empty jackets that have a number written by Bambaataa are also included in numeric order in the boxes.
      - 1 - Dance to the music, 1970; SR-9039-9040; Sly & the Family Stone (Musical group) (Box 128)
        Epic
        New York, New York
      - 1 - Dance to the music, 1969; SR-9039-9040; Sly & the Family Stone (Musical group) (Box 106)
      - 1 - Dance to the music, Sly & the Family Stone (Musical group) (Box 106)
        Empty jacket
      - 2 - Life, 1968; SR-9672; Stone, Sly. (Box 106)
        New York
      - 3 - Whole new thing, 1967; SR-9673; Sly & the Family Stone (Musical group) (Box 106)
      - 4 - Diana Ross presents the Jackson 5., 1969; SR-9642; Jackson 5 (Musical group) (Box 140)
        Motown Records
        Hollywood, California
      - 5 - Third album, 1970; SR-7787; Jackson 5 (Musical group) (Box 106)
        Hollywood, Californialif.
      - 7 - Funkadelic, 1970; SR-9041; Funkadelic (Musical group). (Box 106)
        Westbound Records
        Southfield, Michigan
      - 10 - Come together, Ike & Tina Turner and the Ikettes (Box 106)
      - 11 - Dionne Warwick's greatest motion picture hits., 1969; SR-9042; Warwick, Dionne. (Box 106)
        Scepter Records
      - 14 - Cosmo's factory, 1970; SR-7788; Creedence Clearwater Revival (Musical group), (Box 106)
        Fantasy Records
        Berkeley, California
      - 15 - Jimi Hendrix Experience and Otis Redding., 1970; SR-7789; Hendrix, Jimi. (Box 106)
        Reprise Records
        Burbank, California
      - 16 - Captured live at the Forum, 1969; SR-9043; Three Dog Night (Musical group) (Box 106)
        ABC/Dunhill Records
      - 18 - Hair: the American tribal love-rock musical, 1968; SR-7790; MacDermot, Galt. (Box 106)
        RCA Victor
      - 19 - Mighty Sparrow., 1960-1969; SR-9044; Sparrow (Calypso singer) (Box 106)
        RA
        Barbados
      - 19 - Music is the message, 1971; SR-7791-7792; Kool & the Gang. (Box 106)
        De-Lite Records
        Chicago, Illinois
      - 21 - Best of Sam & Dave., 1969; SR-7793; Sam & Dave. (Box 106)
        Atlantic Records
      - 22 - Right on be free, 1970; SR-7794; Voices of East Harlem. (Box 106)
        Elektra Records
        Los Angeles, California
      - 23 - Live at the Sex Machine, 1971; SR-9643; Kool & the Gang. (Box 140)
      - 23 - Live at the Sex Machine, 1971; SR-7795; Kool & the Gang. (Box 106)
      - 24 - Aretha live at Fillmore West, 1971; SR-7796; Franklin, Aretha. (Box 106)
      - 26 - What you see is what you get: live at Carnegie Hall., 1971; SR-7797-7798 (Box 106)
        United Artists Records: UAS-9953._x000D_
        United Artists Records
      - 28 - Greatest hits of Dionne Warwicke, vol. 1., 1972; SR-7800; Warwick, Dionne. (Box 106)
        H.E.R.O. Records
        Westville, New Jersey
      - 28 - Morning, noon & the Nite-Liters., 1971; SR-7799; Nite-Liters (Musical group) (Box 106)
      - 29 - Diana!., 1971; SR-7801; Ross, Diana, 1944- (Box 106)
        Detroit, Michigan
      - 30 - We got to live together, 1970; SR-9645; Miles, Buddy, (Box 140)
        Mercury Records
        United States
      - 30 - We got to live together, 1970; SR-7802; Miles, Buddy, (Box 106)
      - 31 - What's going on, 1971; SR-9333; Gaye, Marvin. (Box 106)
        Tamla
      - 32 - One world, 1971; SR-7803; Rare Earth (Musical group) (Box 106)
        Rare Earth
      - 33 - Shaft: music from the soundtrack, 1971; SR-9045-9046; Hayes, Isaac. (Box 106)
        Enterprise
        Memphis, Tennessee
      - 34 - Hot pants, 1971; SR-7804; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 106)
        Polydor Records
        Brazil
      - 35 - Soul to soul., 1971; SR-7805 (Box 106)
      - 36 - Tom Jones sings She's a lady., 1971; SR-7806; Jones, Tom, 1940- (Box 106)
        Paris International Records & Filmworks Inc.
        Miami, Florida
      - 38 - Osibisa., 1971; SR-9047; Osibisa (Musical group) (Box 106)
        Decca
      - 38 - It's just begun, Jimmy Castor Bunch (Box 106)
        Empty jacket.
      - 39 - (For God's sake) give more power to the people, 1970; SR-7807; Chi-Lites (Musical group) (Box 106)
        Brunswick Records
      - 40 - First great rock festivals of the seventies: Isle of Wight and Atlanta Pop Festival., 1971; SR-9049-9050 (Box 106)
        Columbia Records
      - 40 - First great rock festivals of the seventies: Isle of Wight and Atlanta Pop Festival., 1971; SR-9048 (Box 106)
      - 42 - Golden bisquits., 1970-1979; SR-9051; Three Dog Night (Musical group) (Box 106)
        Drive
        Hialeah, Florida
      - 43 - Jesus Christ superstar: a rock opera, 1970; SR-7808-7809; Lloyd Webber, Andrew, 1948- (Box 106)
        Original set issue #DXSA 7206; DL 79178 and DL 79179 are issue numbers for each disc._x000D_
      - 44 - Very Dionne., 1960-1969; SR-9052; Warwick, Dionne. (Box 106)
      - 45 - Homemade, 1971; SR-7810 (Box 106)
        MGM Records: SW 93803 (on container: SE-4770)._x000D_
        MGM Records
      - 46 - When I was a kid, 1971; SR-7811; Cosby, Bill, 1937- (Box 107)
        UNI Records
      - 48 - Walt Disney presents the Jungle book, 1967; SR-7812 (Box 107)
        Disko Mania
      - 49 - Revolution of the mind, 1971; SR-9053-9054-9055; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 107)
      - 49 - Revolution of the mind, 1971; SR-7813; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 107)
      - 49 - Revolution of the mind, 1971; SR-7196-7197; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 107)
      - 52 - Santana., 1972; SR-7814; Santana (Musical group) (Box 107)
      - 53 - Buddy Miles live., 1970-1979; SR-7815-7816; Miles, Buddy. (Box 107)
      - 54 - Pain, 1972; SR-7817; Ohio Players (Musical group) (Box 107)
      - 55 - Goin' for myself, 1972; SR-7818; Coffey, Dennis. (Box 107)
        Sussex Records
      - 56 - It's just begun, 1972; SR-9646; Jimmy Castor Bunch. (Box 140)
      - 56 - It's just begun, 1972; SR-6818-SR-6819; Jimmy Castor Bunch. (Box 3)
        This copy used on the Renegades of Rhythm Tour
      - 58 - Brother, brother, brother., 1972; SR-7819; Isley Brothers. (Box 107)
        T-Neck Records
      - 59 - Fats shake 'em up, 1968; SR-7820-7821 (Box 107)
        "The group, now known as "Music by Pritchard," was orginally known as "Mac Beth the Great" (in the early 1950's). After the passing of Mac Beth, the band remained intact under the lead
        Camille Records
      - 60 - America eats its young, 1972; SR-7822-7823; Funkadelic (Musical group) (Box 107)
      - 62 - Bwana., 1972; SR-9056 (Box 107)
        Caytronics
      - 63 - Nature planned it., 1972; SR-7824; Four Tops (Musical group) (Box 107)
      - 64 - Cosmos, 1971; SR-7825; Donaldson, Lou. (Box 107)
        Blue Note
      - 65 - Wildfire, 1972; SR-7826; Bryant, Rusty. (Box 107)
        Prestige: PRST-10037 (on container: PR-10037; 10037)._x000D_ "Promotional copy - not for sale."
        Prestige Records
      - 68 - Music is my life, 1972; SR-7827; Preston, Billy. (Box 107)
        A&M Records
        Beverly Hills, California
      - 71 - From within, 1972; SR-7828-7829; Warwick, Dionne. (Box 107)
      - 72 - Belafonte live, 1972; SR-7830-7831; Belafonte, Harry, 1927- (Box 107)
      - 73 - Superfly, 1972; SR-9647; Mayfield, Curtis. (Box 140)
        Curtom Records
      - 74 - Sweet Salvation., 1972; SR-7832; Sweet Salvation (Musical group) (Box 107)
      - 75 - Phase two, 1972; SR-9057; Jimmy Castor Bunch. (Box 107)
      - 77 - Do you see what I see?, 1972; SR-7833; Bar-Kays (Musical group) (Box 107)
        Volt
      - 79 - Birth day, 1972; SR-7834; New Birth (Musical group) (Box 107)
      - 80 - Heads, 1972; SR-9058; Osibisa (Musical group) (Box 107)
      - 82 - Composite truth, 1973; SR-7835; Mandrill (Musical group) (Box 107)
      - 83 - Masterpiece, 1973; SR-9059; Temptations (Musical group) (Box 107)
        Gordy
      - 84 - Dimension III, 1973; SR-9060; Jimmy Castor Bunch. (Box 107)
        RCA Quadra Disc
      - 85 - Love can make it easier., 1973; SR-7836; Friends of Distinction (Musical group) (Box 107)
      - 86 - Harder they come: (soundtrack)., 1972; SR-9061 (Box 107)
        Mango Records
      - 87 - Wattstax: the living word., 1972; SR-7837-7838 (Box 107)
        Stax Records
      - 89 - Understanding, 1972; SR-7839; Womack, Bobby. (Box 107)
      - 90 - Cymande., 1972; SR-7840 (Box 107)
        Janus Records
      - 90 - Cymande., 1972; SR-9671 (Box 107)
      - 91 - Original soundtrack Black Caesar, 1973; SR-7841; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 108)
      - 92 - Soul makossa., 1970-1979; SR-9062 (Box 108)
        Pathfinder Records
      - 93 - Fresh, 1973; SR-9648; Sly & the Family Stone (Musical group) (Box 140)
      - 94 - Isaac Hayes live at the Sahara Tahoe, 1973; SR-7842-7843; Hayes, Isaac. (Box 108)
      - 95 - Soul makossa, 1972; SR-9063; Dibango, Manu, 1933- (Box 108)
      - 96 - Skull Snaps., 1973; SR-9064; Skull Snaps (Musical group) (Box 108)
        GRP Records
      - 96 - Skull Snaps, Skull Snaps (Box 108)
      - 97 - Everyday People., 1972; SR-7844; Everyday People (Funk group) (Box 108)
        Red Coach
      - 98 - Soul makossa., 1973; SR-9065; Afrique (Musical group) (Box 108)
        Maine Recordings
        England
      - 99 - Back to the world, 1973; SR-9066; Mayfield, Curtis. (Box 108)
      - 100 - Cosmic slop, 1973; SR-9067; Funkadelic (Musical group) (Box 108)
      - 101 - All I need is time., 1973; SR-9068; Knight, Gladys, 1944- (Box 108)
        Soul
      - 103 - Let the good times roll: original soundtrack., 1973; SR-7845-7846 (Box 108)
        Bell Records
      - 104 - London Bo Diddley sessions., 1973; SR-7847; Bo Diddley, 1928-2008. (Box 108)
        Chess Records
      - 105 - Innervisions, 1973; SR-9069; Wonder, Stevie. (Box 108)
      - 108 - Soul Makossa, 1973; SR-7848; OlatuNew Jerseyi, Babatunde. (Box 108)
        Paradise Records
        North Hollywood, California
      - 109 - Wild and peaceful, 1973; SR-9070; Kool & the Gang. (Box 108)
      - 112 - Involved., 1971; SR-9071; Starr, Edwin. (Box 108)
      - 114 - Around the world with Three Dog Night., 1973; SR-7849-7850; Three Dog Night (Musical group) (Box 108)
        Dunhill
      - 115 - Ecstasy, 1973; SR-9072; Ohio Players (Musical group) (Box 108)
      - 118 - It's been a long time, 1973; SR-9650; New Birth (Musical group) (Box 140)
      - 118 - Comin' out; Even though., 1980; SR-7012 (Box 17)
        T.K. Disco
      - 119 - Happy children, 1973; SR-9073; Osibisa (Musical group) (Box 108)
        Warner Brothers Records
      - 121 - Tremendo Cumban, 1963; SR-9074; Machito. (Box 108)
        Tico
      - 122 - Pleasure., 1972; SR-8479; Ohio Players (Musical group) (Box 107)
      - 122 - Pleasure., Ohio Players (Musical group) (Box 108)
      - 123 - 1990, 1973; SR-7851; Whitfield, Norman. (Box 108)
      - 123 - 1990, 1973; SR-7852; Whitfield, Norman, (Box 108)
      - 124 - Love is the message, 1973; SR-7853; MFSB (Musical group) (Box 108)
        Philadelphia International Records
      - 126 - Woyaya, 1971; SR-9075; Osibisa (Musical group) (Box 108)
        Universal City, California
      - 126 - B.Y.O.B. (Bring your own body), 1981; SR-7015; Take Five (Musical group) (Box 19)
        Promotional copy._x000D_ Taken from the Destiny LP, DLA-10002 Take Five.
        Desert Moon Records
      - 127 - Graham Central Station., 1974; SR-9076; Graham Central Station (Musical group) (Box 108)
      - 128 - Open our eyes, 1974; SR-7854; Earth, Wind & Fire (Musical group) (Box 108)
      - 130 - Skin tight, 1974; SR-7855; Ohio Players (Musical group) (Box 108)
      - 131 - Latin-soul-rock., 1974; SR-9077 (Box 108)
        Fania Records
      - 132 - Diana Ross., 1970; SR-9078; Ross, Diana, 1944- (Box 108)
      - 133 - Glitter, 1972; SR-7856; Glitter, Gary, (Box 108)
      - 134 - Small talk, 1974; SR-9079; Sly & the Family Stone (Musical group) (Box 108)
      - 135 - Comin' from all ends, 1974; SR-7857; New Birth (Musical group) (Box 108)
      - 135 - Live in London., 1974; SR-7858 (Box 108)
      - 137 - New ways but love stays., 1970; SR-7859; Supremes (Musical group) (Box 108)
      - 138 - Motown at the Hollywood Palace., 1970; SR-7860 (Box 109)
      - 140 - Together brothers original motion picture soundtrack., 1974; SR-7861; White, Barry, 1944-2003. (Box 109)
        20th Century Fox Records
      - 141 - Soulful Christmas, 1968; SR-9080; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 109)
        Kimsha Records
        Brooklyn, New York
      - 142 - Mud Slide Slim and the blue horizon, 1971; SR-7862; Taylor, James, 1948- (Box 109)
      - 144 - Love's lines, angles and rhymes, 1971; SR-9081; 5th Dimension (Musical group) (Box 109)
      - 145 - Through the ages, 1973; SR-7863; Wolfman Jack, 1939-1995. (Box 109)
        Wooden Nickel; Manufactured and distributed by RCA
      - 146 - Isleys live, 1973; SR-7864-7865; Isley Brothers. (Box 109)
      - 148 - Love, peace & soul., 1972; SR-7866 (Box 109)
        Hot Buttered Soul
      - 149 - Evening with Ronnie, 1973; SR-9082; Butler, Ronnie, 1937-2017. (Box 109)
        R and R Records
        Nassau, Bahamas
      - 150 - Secrets of the pan, 1970; SR-9083; Gay Flamingoes (Musical group) (Box 109)
        Antillana
        Ont., Californianada
      - 152 - You're so beautiful, 1971; SR-7867; Wright, Charles, 1940- (Box 109)
      - 152 - You're so beautiful, 1971; SR-7868; Wright, Charles, 1940- (Box 109)
      - 153 - Release yourself, 1974; SR-8013; Graham Central Station (Musical group) (Box 114)
      - 154 - Life, 1973; SR-9084; Exuma. (Box 109)
        Kama Sutra
      - 155 - Disco par-r-rty., 1973; SR-9085 (Box 109)
        Spring Records
      - 157 - Calypso carnival. Vol. 1, 1974; SR-9086; Sandpebbles of Barbados (Musical group) (Box 109)
        Matrix / Runout (side 1): PG-1011-S1; Matrix / Runout (side 2): PG-1011-S2.
        Paul Winley Records
      - 158 - Discs of gold, 1974; SR-9328; Independents (Musical group) (Box 109)
        Wand
      - 159 - Carolina county ball, Elf (Box 109)
      - 160 - Mejor de Barrabas., 1974; SR-7870; Barrabas (Musical group) (Box 109)
        Arcano Records
      - 161 - Death wish, 1974; SR-9087; Hancock, Herbie, 1940- (Box 109)
      - 162 - Ice, 1974; SR-7871; Lafayette Afro Rock Band. (Box 109)
      - 163 - Real, 1974; SR-7872; Carter, Clarence, 1936- (Box 109)
        ABC Records
      - 164 - Three Degrees., 1973; SR-9088; Three Degrees (Musical group) (Box 109)
        Philadelphia International Records: Distributed by CBS Records
      - 166 - Revolution will not be televised, 1974; SR-9089; Scott-Heron, Gil, 1949-2011. (Box 109)
        Flo-Feel Records
        Elmhurst, New York
      - 166 - Revolution will not be televised, Scott-Heron, Gil, 1949-2011. (Box 109)
      - 168 - Euphrates River., 1974; SR-7873; Main Ingredient (Musical group) (Box 109)
      - 170 - Kids and me., 1974; SR-7874; Preston, Billy. (Box 109)
      - 171 - Finger pointers, 1974; SR-7875; Choice Four (Musical group) (Box 109)
      - 172 - Cosmic vortex: (Justice divine), 1974; SR-7876; Irvine, Weldon. (Box 109)
      - 173 - Rockin' soul., 1974; SR-7877 (Box 109)
      - 174 - Rashida, 1973; SR-7878; Lucien, Jon. (Box 109)
      - 175 - Introducing Roshell Anderson, 1974; SR-7879 (Box 109)
        Sunburst Records
      - 176 - Trustmaker., 1974; SR-7880; Tymes (Musical group) (Box 109)
      - 177 - Mott the Hoople live., 1974; SR-7881 (Box 109)
      - 178 - All the faces of Buddy Miles, 1974; SR-9090; Miles, Buddy. (Box 109)
      - 179 - Caterpillar, 1974; SR-9091; Carib Tokyo Steel Orchestra (Box 109)
        Straker's Records
      - 179 - Rufusized, 1974; SR-7882; Rufus (Musical group) (Box 109)
      - 180 - Keep on steppin', 1974; SR-9092; Fatback (Musical group) (Box 109)
        Essiebons Enterprises Ltd.
        Accra, Ghana
      - 181 - Warrior, 1973; SR-7883; Egnos, Bertha. (Box 109)
      - 182 - Fire, 1974; SR-9093; Ohio Players (Musical group) (Box 109)
      - 183 - Wuk up yur ass with Laviscount Brass, 1974; SR-9094; Laviscount Brass (Musical group) (Box 109)
        Trinidad & Tobago
      - 184 - Nightbirds, 1974; SR-9095; Labelle (Musical group) (Box 110)
      - 185 - Borboletta, 1974; SR-7884; Santana (Musical group), (Box 110)
      - 185 - Sorry; That's the trouble, 1976; SR-7885; Jones, Grace. (Box 110)
        Beam Junction
      - I need a man, 1977; SR-7886; Jones, Grace. (Box 110)
        Not numbered, cataloged with SR-7885. Beam Junction: 12-BJ 1004.
      - 186 - Perfect angel., 1974; SR-9096; Riperton, Minnie. (Box 110)
      - 187 - Live it up, 1974; SR-9097; Isley Brothers. (Box 110)
      - 188 - Chastisement, 1972; SR-7887; Last Poets (Group) (Box 110)
        Blue Thumb
      - 191 - Reality, Brown, James (Box 110)
      - 192 - 25889, 1971; SR-7888; John, Elton. (Box 110)
      - 193 - Curtis, 1970; SR-9098; Mayfield, Curtis. (Box 110)
      - 195 - World is a ghetto, 1972; SR-7889; War (Musical group) (Box 110)
      - 196 - Deliver the word., 1973; SR-7890; War (Musical group) (Box 110)
      - 197 - Live, 1971; SR-7891-7892; 5th Dimension (Musical group) (Box 110)
      - 198 - Greatest hits of Frankie Valli and the fabulous Four Seasons., 1974; SR-7893-7896; Valli, Frankie. (Box 110)
        London Records
      - 199 - Don't stop the carnival, 1970-1979; SR-9099; Merrymen (Musical group) (Box 110)
        Caravan
        Scarborough, Ontario
      - 201 - 200 motels: original motion picture soundtrack, 1971; SR-7897-7898; Zappa, Frank. (Box 110)
      - 202 - Song for you, 1975; SR-9100; Temptations (Musical group) (Box 110)
      - 203 - Wild Magnolias., 1974; SR-9101; Wild Magnolias (Musical group) (Box 110)
      - 204 - Mark of the beast, 1974; SR-7899; Hutch, Willie. (Box 110)
      - 205 - Disc-o-tex and his sex-o-lettes review, Disc-o-Tex and his Sex-o-lettes (Box 110)
      - 206 - Thrust., 1974; SR-9102; Hancock, Herbie, 1940- (Box 110)
      - 207 - Chocolate City, 1975; SR-9103; Parliament (Musical group) (Box 110)
        Casablanca Records
      - 208 - More drums of passion, 1966; SR-7900; OlatuNew Jerseyi, Babatunde. (Box 110)
      - 209 - Sex machine today, 1975; SR-9104-9105; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 110)
      - 210 - That's the way of the world, 1975; SR-7901; Earth, Wind & Fire (Musical group), (Box 110)
      - 211 - Do wah nanny, 1971; SR-7902; Exuma. (Box 110)
      - 212 - Live carnival time, 1975; SR-9106; Milo and the Kings (Musical group) (Box 110)
      - 213 - Foxy Brown, 1974; SR-7903; Hutch, Willie. (Box 110)
      - 215 - Wiz; the super soul musical Wonderful Wizard of Oz. Music & lyrics by Charlie Smalls. Book by William F. Brown. Orchestrations by Harold Wheeler, SR-7904; Smalls, Charlie. (Box 110)
      - 216 - Closeup., 1975; SR-7905; Valli, Frankie. (Box 110)
        Private I Records
      - 217 - Calypso carnival, 1971; SR-9107; Belafonte, Harry, 1927- (Box 110)
      - 218 - Out among 'em, 1975; SR-7906; Love Child's Afro-Cuban Blues Band. (Box 110)
        Roulette
      - 219 - Let's take it to the stage, 1975; SR-9108-9109; Funkadelic (Musical group) (Box 110)
      - 220 - Magic disco machine, 1975; SR-7907; Disc-o-tech (Musical group) (Box 110)
      - 221 - Yum, yum, 1975; SR-9110; Fatback (Musical group) (Box 110)
        Event Records: EV 6904 (on container: 6904)._x000D_
        Event Records
      - 222 - New and improved., 1974; SR-7908 (Box 110)
      - 223 - Ain't no 'bout-a-doubt it, Graham Central Station (Box 110)
      - 224 - Carnival '75, 1975; SR-7909 (Box 110)
        Dynamic Artists
        Richmond, Virginia